Guide to the Woman’s Student Government Association Records, 1919-1974
Duke University. University Archives
Woman’s Student Government Association records 1919-1974
Duke University. University Archives
Duke University. Woman's Student Government Association.
13.8 linear feet Extent: 12,100 Items
The Woman's Student Government Association (WSGA) was formed in 1918, and the organization continued when the Woman's College was incorporated on East Campus in 1930. The WSGA was responsible for the "regulat[ion] of all matters pertaining to the life of the women of the Woman's College of Duke University, not under the jurisdiction of the Faculty." This autonomy along with the segregated campus life style of the coordinate college allowed female students to develop leadership skills and confidence that an integrated student government may not have allowed them to gain. Collection contains minutes, correspondence, reports, printed matter, memos, clippings, and other official records of the WSGA and its committees, along with records of several student organizations and documents generated by the administrations of the Woman's College and Duke University. Materials range in date from 1919-1974.
UA.31.02.0004
Language: Material in English
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
In accordance with the Family Education Rights and Privacy Act of 1974 as amended, Duke University permits students to inspect their education records and limits the disclosure of personally identifiable information from education records.
Researchers must register and agree to copyright and privacy laws before using this collection.
Provenance
The Woman’s Student Government Association Records were received by the University Archives as a transfer in 1974-1997.
Historical Note
The Woman's College was established in 1930, as coordinate college to Trinity College for men, with the appointment of Alice M. Baldwin as Dean of the Woman's College. Prior to that women had a long history of attending Trinity College (the antecedent of Duke University). Three Giles sisters were awarded degrees in 1878 on the basis of private instruction by faculty members before Trinity College moved to Durham in 1892. In 1892 the Board of Trinity College officially admitted women to the college, and the first women to attend regular classes graduated in 1896. These women had been permitted to attend classes but they were not given residence on the campus.
In 1896, Washington Duke made a gift of $100,000 to Trinity College urging that women be admitted "on equal footing with men." A small dormitory, the Mary Duke Building was subsequently built in 1898; however it was torn down in 1912. It was replaced by Southgate dormitory for women in 1921. The increase in women students during World War I gave rise to the instatement of a Dean of Women, Martha Buchanan, as well as the formation of the Woman's Student Government in 1918. In 1924, Alice M. Baldwin was named Dean of Women. Upon reflection of her early years at Trinity College Alice Baldwin notes:
When I first came to Trinity, it was primarily a man's college, run by men, where some women had studied for years, it is true, but where women had no part in administration except to some extent in the social life and the management of the one women's dormitory.
With the creation of the coordinate Woman's College this gradually began to change and women (administrators and students) were given more control over East Campus.
The Woman's Student Government Association was formed in 1918 and its purpose listed in the 1922 amended constitution was "to preserve student honor, to develop self-control, and to govern the young women matriculated of the College." In order to fulfill these functions the Association mandated that several committees should be formed including a social committee, social service committee, social standards committee, and room committee plus a journal, publicity, and social room committees.
With the incorporation of the Woman's College in 1930 the purpose of the Woman's Student Government Association (WSGA) of Duke University broadened to encompass "regulat[ion] of all matters pertaining to the life of the women of the Woman's College of Duke University, not under the jurisdiction of the Faculty." Furthermore the organization was "to increase a sense of individual responsibility; to further a spirit of unity among the women of the College; and to cooperate with the Faculty in creating and maintaining high ideals for the Women of the University."
Therefore the WSGA in cooperation with the Administrative staff of the College was responsible for the formation and enforcement of the regulations for the Woman's College. These regulations include those related to specific classes (i.e. freshmen, upperclassmen, etc.), general social regulations (drinking, smoking, automobiles, dates), house regulations (closing/quiet hours, men callers, late leaves, serenades), off-campus regulations (Durham area restaurants, hotels), and social standards regulations (attire on campus, off campus, and behavior becoming to Woman's College students).
The segregated campus life style of the coordinate college allowed female students to develop leadership skills and confidence that an integrated student government may not have allowed them to gain. For "in addition to the judicial board, the Woman's Student Government Association consisted of a strong network of dorm representatives and legislators." Upon reflection most alumnae said that they appreciated the leadership experiences inherit in the creation of policy and self-discipline. Indeed the Woman's College produced many political and cultural luminaries including: Elizabeth Dole; Ann K. Covington; Nancy Hanks; Eleanor Smeal; Margaret Taylor Smith; and Anne Tyler.
During the 1960s a perpetual request from the student body was the liberalizing of social regulations, especially those that were traditionally imposed upon women and not on men. This issue became a driving-force in the creation of a university unified student government, and in 1967 the student body voted to merge the Men's Student Government and the Woman's Student Government Association creating the Associated Students of Duke University (ASDU). Valerie Ann Mosley (1980) was the first female president of ASDU. In 1972, the consolidation of the two separate colleges became complete when the Board of Trustees approved the merger of the Woman's College and Trinity College.
Works cited
"President Few and the Woman's College" in folder 1198, William Preston Few Records and Papers, University Archives, Duke University.
"WSGA Amendments, 1922," Box 7, Woman's Student Government Association records, University Archives, Duke University.
1930 Woman's College Handbook, University Archives, Duke University.
Daub, Tammy. "Smashing the Glass Ceiling," The Chronicle 11 October 1996.
ibid. and Arnold, Autumn ,"White Gloves and Parlor Games," The Chronicle 18 January 2006.
Collection Overview
Extent: 13.7 linear ft. (22 Hollinger boxes + 1 flat box)
Contents: Minutes, correspondence, reports, printed matter, memos, clippings, and other official records of the WSGA and its committees, along with records of several student organizations and documents generated by the administrations of the Woman's College and Duke University. Subjects include the honor system, class reports, dormitory life, athletics, elections, freshman orientation, social organizations, handbooks, celebrations, and social regulations. The collection includes materials, such as handbooks and surveys, received from other schools, and publications and other material from the National Student Association.
Organization: Series: 1. WSGA Minutes; 2. Correspondence; 3. Subject files; 4. Materials from other colleges; 5. National Student Association; 6. Account books; 7. Student Organizations; 8. Oversize
Restriction: Judicial Board case files closed except by permission, University Archivist. Some folders may contain information restricted by FERPA.
Subject Headings
Duke University. Associated Students of Duke University; Duke University. Student Government; Duke University -- Students; Duke University -- Students -- Political activity; Duke University -- Students -- Societies, etc.; Duke University. Woman’s Student Government Association; Duke University. Woman’s Student Government Association. Social Standards Committee; Student participation in administration
Related Material
Associated Students of Duke University records, 1965-1993.
University Archives, Duke University.
Woman’s College records, 1928-1974.
University Archives, Duke University.
Contents of Collection
- WSGA Minutes, 1920-1968, 4 Boxes
  - Folder title (Box 1)
  - WSGA-Association Minutes, 1921-1929 (Box 1)
  - WSGA-Association Minutes, 1930-1939 (Box 1)
  - WSGA-Association Minutes, 1940-1949 (Box 1)
  - WSGA-Association Minutes and Agenda, 1950-1959 (2 folders) (Box 1)
  - WSGA-Association Meeting Notes (Council Meetings), April 7, 1947-March 15, 1948 (Box 1)
  - WSGA-Association Meeting Minutes, April 2, 1945-March 4, 1947 (Box 1)
  - WSGA Council Minutes, April 1, 1946-April 2, 1947 (Box 1)
  - WSGA-Association Meeting Minutes (Council Meetings), April 6, 1948-April 5, 1949 (Box 1)
  - WSGA Assembly Minutes and Agenda, 1960-1963 (Box 1)
  - WSGA Council Minutes, 1928-1930 (Box 2)
  - WSGA Council Minutes and Agenda, 1950-1951 (Box 2)
  - WSGA Council Minutes, 1952-1953 (Box 2)
  - WSGA Council Minutes, 1954-1956 (Box 2)
  - WSGA Council Minutes and Agenda, 1956-1959 (Box 2)
  - WSGA Council Minutes and Agenda, 1960-1961 (Box 2)
  - WSGA Council Minutes, 1962-1963 (Box 2)
  - WSGA Executive Council Minutes, 1929-1933 (Box 3)
  - WSGA Executive Council Minutes, 1933-1935 (Box 3)
  - WSGA Executive Council Minutes, 1935-1937 (Box 3)
  - WSGA Executive Council Minutes, 1937-1939 (Box 3)
  - WSGA Executive Council Minutes, 1940-1942 (Box 3)
  - WSGA Executive Council Minutes, 1943-1944 (Box 3)
  - WSGA Executive Council Minutes, 1945 (Box 3)
  - WSGA Executive Council Minutes, 1946-1949 (Box 3)
  - WSGA Executive Council Minutes, 1956-1957 (Box 3)
  - WSGA Legislature Minutes and Agenda, 1965-1966 (Box 4)
  - WSGA Legislature Minutes and Agenda, 1967-1968 (Box 4)
  - WSGA Legislature Proposals and Resolutions, undated (Box 4)
  - WSGA Legislature Minutes and Agenda, 1966-1967(2 folders) (Box 4)
  - WSGA Student Council Minutes, 1920-1929 (Box 4)
  - WSGA Student Council Minutes, 1930-1931 (Box 4)
- Correspondence, 1923-1971, 2 Boxes
  - WSGA Correspondence, 1923-1930 (Box 5)
  - WSGA Correspondence, 1935, 1937-1938, 1941 (Box 5)
  - WSGA Correspondence, 1949, 1955-1956, 1958, 1959 (Box 5)
  - WSGA Correspondence, 1943-1945 (Box 5)
  - WSGA Correspondence, 1961-1962 (Box 5)
  - WSGA Correspondence, 1963-1965 (Box 5)
  - WSGA Correspondence, 1966-1967 (2 folders) (Box 5)
  - WSGA Correspondence, 1968 (Box 5)
  - WSGA Correspondence, 1971 (Box 5)
  - WSGA Academic Honor Code Correspondence, 1947-1948 (Box 6)
- Subject files, 1919-1972, 11 Boxes
  - Academic Honor System Memos, Newspaper clippings, misc., 1963-1965 and undated (Box 6)
  - Alumnae Association of Women's College Misc., 1965, 1968-1969, 1971-1972 (Box 6)
  - American Government Committee Report, 1963-1964 (Box 6)
  - Association of Women's Residence Misc., 1967, 1970-1972 (Box 6)
  - Board System, 1968, 1970-1971 (Box 6)
  - WSGA Budgets, 1964-1967 (Box 6)
  - Building Commission-East Campus Student Center, 1961, 1963-1964 (Box 6)
  - Building Plans and Renovations-East Campus, 1966 (Box 6)
  - Campus Community Council, 1971-1972 (Box 6)
  - Chartering Procedures, 1962, 1964, undated (Box 6)
  - Chronicle Articles, 1961-1962 (Box 6)
  - Chronicle Articles, 1962-1963 (Box 6)
  - Chronicle Articles, 1963-1964 (Box 6)
  - Chronicle Articles, 1962-1964 (Box 6)
  - Chronicle Articles, 1965-1966 (Box 6)
  - Chronicle Articles, 1966-1967 (Box 6)
  - Claremont Trip, 1967 (2 folders) (Box 6)
  - WSGA Annual Class Reports, 1926-1930 (Box 6)
  - Class Representative Annual Reports, 1959-1964 (Box 6)
  - WSGA Class Structure: Reevaluation of it as Basis for Student Government Organization, 1966-1967 (Box 6)
  - Code of Campus Living Revisions and Final, 1963-1965 (Box 7)
  - WSGA Monthly and Annual Committee Reports, 1921-1929 (Box 7)
  - Committee for Evaluation of Woman's College Regulations-Minutes, 1966 (Box 7)
  - Community Council of Woman's College Constitution, By-Laws, Minutes, 1969-1971 (Box 7)
  - WSGA Constitution and By-Laws, 1930(?), 1963, 1965 (Box 7)
  - WSGA Amendments, Constitution, and Regulations, 1926-1927 (Box 7)
  - WSGA Amendments, 1922 (Box 7)
  - Amendments to Constitution, 1971-1972 (Box 7)
  - Council of Student Body Presidents, Duke University (Box 7)
  - WSGA Course Evaluations, 1963 (Box 7)
  - Cunningham, Suzie-Speeches, President of WSGA, 1965-1966 (Box 7)
  - Cut System, 1951-1952, 1961-1963 (Box 7)
  - Dining Halls Memos and Announcements, 1966 and 1969 (Box 7)
  - Change in Drinking Regulations, 1967-1968 (Box 7)
  - Dormitories Announcements, Memos, Policies, etc.,, 1963-1971 (Box 7)
  - Dormitories-Living, Learning Corridors (Box 7)
  - Dormitories-User's Committee for New East Campus Dorm, 1968 (Box 7)
  - Dormitories-Visiting Hours for Men (open-opens), 1968-1971 (Box 7)
  - Dormitories Meeting Minutes, 1928-1929 (Box 7)
  - Dormitories-University Caucus, Student Life Committee: Evaluation of Women's Living Group Regulations and Proposals (Box 7)
  - WSGA Dormitory Association Minutes, 1924-1930 (Box 7)
  - Driving Time Sheets (Box 7)
  - WSGA Coordinate Board Constitution, 1960, 1962 (Box 8)
  - WSGA Coordinate Board, Academic Freedom (American Civil Liberties Union and National Student Association Publications), 1959 (Box 8)
  - Coordinate Board Annual Reports, 1960-1964 (Box 8)
  - Coordinate Board Evaluation, 1960-1963 (Box 8)
  - Coordinate Board Course Guide, 1961 (Box 8)
  - Coordinate Board Exam Schedule, 1961-1962 (Box 8)
  - WSGA Coordinate Board Minutes, Reports, and Correspondence, 1952-1957 (Box 8)
  - WSGA Coordinate Board Minutes, Reports, and Correspondence, 1957-1960 (Box 8)
  - Coordinate Board Minutes, Correspondence, 1960-1961 (Box 8)
  - Coordinate Board Misc., 1960-62, 1941 (Box 8)
  - Coordinate Board Misc. Projects, 1960-1963 (Box 8)
  - Coordinate Board Student Faculty Relations, 1961-1962 (Box 8)
  - WSGA-Educated Women Power, 1967 (Box 9)
  - WSGA-Educational Affairs Committee, 1964-1966 (Box 9)
  - WSGA-Educational Affairs Committee Exam File (2 folders) (Box 9)
  - WSGA-Directions for Educated Women Committee, 1970 (Box 9)
  - Educational Facilities Committee, 1963-1964 (Box 9)
  - WSGA-Election Information, 1950 (Box 9)
  - Election Information, 1964-1967 (Box 9)
  - Election Procedures, 1955 (Box 9)
  - Election Procedure, 1964 (Box 9)
  - Elections, 1928-1929, undated (Box 9)
  - WSGA-Elections, Candidates' Platforms, 1956-1966, 1968 (Box 9)
  - WSGA-Evaluation Report, 1959 (Box 9)
  - Freshman Advisory Council, 1961-1962, 1966-1968 (Box 10)
  - WSGA-Freshman Orientation Week, 1954-1959 (Box 10)
  - Freshman Orientation Week, 1960-1963 (Box 10)
  - Freshman Orientation Week, 1964, 1965, 1966 (Box 10)
  - Freshman Orientation Week, 1967, 1968 (Box 10)
  - Freshman Orientation Week, 1963, 1966, 1968, 1969, undated (Box 10)
  - Woman's College Handbook Advisors'/Editors' Reports, 1963-1964 (Box 10)
  - Handbook Exams, 1964, 1966, 1967, 1968 (Box 10)
  - Honor Code Correspondence and Misc., 1950-1959 (Box 10)
  - Honor Code Plan No. 2, 1957-1958 (Box 10)
  - WSGA-Proposed Honor Code, 1957 (Box 10)
  - Honor Code Campaign, Oct.-Nov. 1957 (Box 10)
  - Academic Honor Code (200 level), 1958-1959 (Box 10)
  - Honor Code-Poll of Woman's College, 1967 (Box 10)
  - WSGA-Honor Pledges, 1921-1924, 1925-1926 (Box 10)
  - WSGA-House Association Minutes, 1927-1928 (Box 10)
  - House President Annual Reports, 1928-1930 (Box 10)
  - House Presidents' Board, 1959-1960 (Box 10)
  - Human Relations Coordinating Committee, 1961 (Box 10)
  - House Counselors, 1964-1971 (Box 10)
  - Inter-government Council, 1966-1967 (Box 10)
  - Inter-campus Council Minutes and Reports, 1963-1965 (Box 10)
  - International Student Committee, 1963-1964, 1966, 1968-1969 (Box 10)
  - WSGA-Ivy Constitution, 1938-1939 (Box 10)
  - Judicial Board-Chronicle Articles, 1965? (Box 11)
  - Judicial Board-Candidates, 1967 (Box 11)
  - Judicial Board-Amendment to Judicial Code, 1970 (Box 11)
  - Judicial Board-Guidelines for House Counselors for Presenting Woman's College Regulations, 1964, 1966 (Box 11)
  - Judicial Board-Judicial Code, 1967 (Box 11)
  - Judicial Board-Form Letters to Students, House Counselors and Parents, 1966, 1967,1970 (Box 11)
  - Judicial Board-Guideposts (Student Guide to College Social Regulations), 1968 (Box 11)
  - Judicial Board-"Ideal Rule Code" Project, 1966 (summer) (Box 11)
  - Judicial Board-Membership (Box 11)
  - WSGA-Judicial Board Minutes, Reports, Misc., 1950-1959 (2 folders) (Box 11)
  - Judicial Board Minutes, Agenda, 1966 (Box 11)
  - Judicial Board Misc., 1937-1970 (Box 11)
  - Judicial Board-Procedure Manual for House Judicial Representatives, 1967 (Box 11)
  - Judicial Board-National Student Association, 1963 (Box 11)
  - Judicial Board Policies, 1960-1963, undated (Box 11)
  - Judicial Board Policies, 1964-1967, 1970, undated (Box 11)
  - Judicial Board-Judicial Procedures "Watson Committee," 1968-1969 (2 folders) (Box 11)
  - Judicial Board Procedures, 1965, 1967 (Box 11)
  - Judicial Board Proposals, 1968 (Box 11)
  - Judicial Board Regulations-Proposed Changes, 1967 (Box 11)
  - WSGA-Judicial Board Report, May 4, 1949 (Box 11)
  - Judicial Board Reports, 1960-1963, 1965-1967 (Box 11)
  - Judicial Board Research Committee, 1963-1965,undated (Box 11)
  - Judicial Board-Review of Woman's College Regulations, 1961 (Box 11)
  - WSGA-Judicial Board Rule Changes, 1945-1948 (Box 11)
  - (Box 12 - RESTRICTED)
  - WSGA-Executive Committee Minutes (Honor Code Violations), 1925-1929 (Box 12 - RESTRICTED)
  - Judicial Board "Call-Downs," 1921-1922 (Box 12 - RESTRICTED)
  - Judicial Board-Cases and Penalties, 1943-1945 (Box 12 - RESTRICTED)
  - Judicial Board-Correspondence, 1941 (Box 12 - RESTRICTED)
  - WSGA-Judicial Board Penalties, 1926-1928 (Box 12 - RESTRICTED)
  - WSGA-Judicial Board Penalties "Call-Downs," 1922-1926 (Box 12 - RESTRICTED)
  - WSGA-Judicial Board Minutes, 1929-1933 (Box 12 - RESTRICTED)
  - Judicial Board-Stealing Case, 1968, 1969-1970 (Box 12 - RESTRICTED)
  - WSGA-Executive Committee Minutes (Honor Code Violations) (Box 12 - RESTRICTED)
  - WSGA-Judicial Board Penalties, 1928-1929 (Box 12 - RESTRICTED)
  - Lansing Campus Letter, 1953-1958 (Box 13)
  - WSGA-Leadership Training Program, 1957-1958 (Box 13)
  - Leadership Training Program, 1958, 1960 (Box 13)
  - WSGA Legislature-Campus Issues Questionnaire, 1966 (Box 13)
  - WSGA Legislature Minutes and Agenda, 1964-1965 (2 folders) (Box 13)
  - Legislature Standing Committee Reports, Misc. (Box 13)
  - Long-Range Planning-Parker, 1958-1960 (Box 13)
  - Ad-Hoc Committee on Living-Learning Experiments (Box 13)
  - Maintenance Committee Annual Report, 1961-1962 (Box 13)
  - WSGA-May Day Report, 1922 (Box 13)
  - May Day Revels, 1926, 1928, 1930, 1931, 1934-1939 (Box 13)
  - WSGA-Membership Rolls, 1921-1925 (Box 13)
  - WSGA-Membership Roll, 1927-1928 (Box 13)
  - WSGA Miscellany (Box 13)
  - Miscellaneous, 1968-1969 (Box 13)
  - WSGA Miscellaneous Articles, 1971-1972,undated (Box 13)
  - National Student Association Committee, 1959, 1964 undated (Box 13)
  - WSGA Newsletter, 1964-1966 (Box 13)
  - N.C.C., 1968 (Box 13)
  - WSGA-N.C. State Legislature, 1967 (Box 13)
  - N.C. Student Legislature and National Student Conference, 1964 (Box 13)
  - WSGA-N.C. Student Legislature Assembly (Box 13)
  - Miscellaneous Notes, 1947 (Box 13)
  - Off-Campus Issues, 1963, 1971 (Box 14)
  - WSGA Officers, Legislators, Committee Chairman, etc. (Box 14)
  - Parliamentary Procedure (Box 14)
  - Official Pronouncement, 1966-1970 (Box 14)
  - Opinion Poll, 1962 (Box 14)
  - Pay Day, 1963-1964 (Box 14)
  - WSGA-Point System, 1921-1926 (Box 14)
  - WSGA-Point System, 1927-1928 (Box 14)
  - WSGA-Point System, 1935-1939 (Box 14)
  - Philosophy Committee Minutes, Reports, 1966, 1967 (Box 14)
  - Philosophy Committee-Academic Freedom/Student Rights (Box 14)
  - East Campus Policy Committee, 1969 (Box 14)
  - WSGA-Annual President's Report, 1950-1958 (Box 14)
  - WSGA-President's File Miscellany, 1957-1958 (Box 14)
  - President's Reports, 1959-1964 (Box 14)
  - President-Advice Letters from Outgoing President to Incoming President (Box 14)
  - Purchasing Bills and Requisitions, 1966 (Box 14)
  - WSGA-Recommendations to Staff, 1936-1937 (Box 15)
  - WSGA-Recommendations to Staff, 1940-1946 (Box 15)
  - WSGA-Regulations, 1970-1971 (Box 15)
  - Scholarship Committee, 1964-1967 (Box 15)
  - WSGA-Secretary Annual Reports, 1928-1930, 1961-1966 (Box 15)
  - WSGA-Secretariat Manual and Misc., 1963-1965 (Box 15)
  - WSGA-Secretary Notes for Minutes of Association and Council, 1944-1946 (Box 15)
  - WSGA-Secretary Notes for Minutes of Association and Council, 1946-1947 (Box 15)
  - Social Code, 1919, 1921 (Box 15)
  - Social Code Dorm Discussions, 1959 (Box 15)
  - Social-Cultural Committee Report, 1965-1966 (Box 15)
  - Social Regulations (Box 15)
  - Social Standards Committee (Box 15)
  - WSGA-Social Standards Committee Annual Reports and Misc., 1930, 1958-1964 (Box 15)
  - WSGA-Sorority Evaluation, 1964-1965? (Box 15)
  - Southern Inter-Collegiate Association of Student Government, 1925-1929 (Box 15)
  - Speeches, 1966, 1968 (Box 16)
  - Woman's College Staff (Box 16)
  - Student Building Commission, 1963-1964 (Box 16)
  - Student Center-East, 1961-1962 (Box 16)
  - Student Exchange Committee Correspondence, Notes, Misc., 1963-1965 (Box 16)
  - Student Faculty Administration Committee Minutes, etc., 1962-1963 (Box 16)
  - Student Faculty Administration Committee Minutes, etc., 1963-1966 (Box 16)
  - Student Government Philosophy and Ideas (Box 16)
  - Student Lists (Box 16)
  - Student Residential Life, 1969 (Box 16)
  - WSGA-Student Staff Committee Minutes, 1950-1951 (Box 16)
  - WSGA-Student Tutoring, 1963 (Box 16)
  - Student Welfare Committee Reports and Correspondence, 1965-1966 (Box 16)
  - Students-Misc. Announcements, Bulletins, Memos, etc. (Box 16)
  - Study Abroad Questionnaire, 1963, 1964 (Box 16)
  - Council-Treasurer and Assistant Treasurer Reports, 1928-1930, 1960-1963 (Box 16)
  - Council-Treasurer Correspondence and Misc., 1967-1969 (Box 16)
  - University Committees-Student Representatives (Box 16)
  - Vice President Annual Reports, 1930, 1950-1951, 1955-1965 (Box 16)
  - Town Girl Representative Annual Report, 1928-1930 (Box 16)
  - Visiting Scholar in Residence (Box 16)
  - "Voice of the Campus" Committee (Box 16)
  - Woman's Residence Council Correspondence and Misc., 1970-1971 (Box 16)
  - Woman's Residence Council Minutes (Box 16)
  - Woman's Residence Council Misc., 1971-1972 (Box 16)
- Materials from other colleges, 1959-1967, 1 Box
  - American University Handbook "Coed Code," 1966-1967 (Box 17)
  - Antioch College Student Government (Box 17)
  - Douglass College Handbook "The Red Book," 1966-1967 (Box 17)
  - Goucher College Freshman Handbook, 1965-1966, 1966-1967 (Box 17)
  - Oberlin College Student Handbook, 1965 (Box 17)
  - Pembroke College Student Handbook, 1964-1965 (Box 17)
  - Pomona College Social Regulations for Women Students, 1966 (Box 17)
  - Radcliffe College Student Handbook, 1962 (Box 17)
  - Sarah Lawrence College Handbook, 1966-1967 (Box 17)
  - Skidmore College Student Handbook, 1966-1967 (Box 17)
  - Smith College Student Handbook, 1966-1967 (Box 17)
  - Swarthmore College Bulletin, 1965-1966 (Box 17)
  - University of Arizona Women's Handbook, 1966-1967 (Box 17)
  - University of Chicago Student Handbook, 1962-1964 (Box 17)